

# Adarsh k l

Phone: +91-8310427818

Github: https://github.com/adarshkl1310

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/adarsh-kl-084435149/

E-mail: im.adarshkl@gmail.com

Website: https://adarshkl1310.github.io/Adarsh/

## CAREER OBJECTIVE



My passion for building great user-centric Full Stack applications on the web gives me great pleasure in my work. I would like to invest my immense drive in creating art on the web to achieve great organizational growth along with personal development in the field.

## PERSONAL PROFILE



Experienced Ruby and Ruby on Rails developer ability to writing clean, efficient, and accessible code in a functional framework. Committed to the total development life cycle, the maintenance of code quality, and bug-free application. Comfortable with HTML-5, CSS-3, Bootstrap-3, Java-Script, version control, Docker, and cloud platforms.

### WORK EXPERIENCE



#### Cool pals services Pvt Ltd in Bangaluru (1/7/2016 to 1/9/2017)

Role: Junior ruby on rails developer (Developed Ruby on Rails applications and supported client user migration and platform upgrades.

#### Codekyt software Pvt Ltd in Chandigarh (1/6/2018 to 2/3/2019)

Role: Full-stack web developer. Week wise convert database data to chart - client f45 challenge, Designed static web application in word press, Developed restful API using rails for the android team )

#### Relyon Softech Pvt Ltd in Bangaluru (1-9-2019 to 30-5-2020)

Role: Full-stack web developer working on a bug fix Saral pay pack web app and Saral TDS.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS



#### **UX UI & Product Design**

- UX Research, Information Architecture, Wireframes, UI Design & Hi-Fi Prototyping.
- Visual Design and High Fidelity Prototypes in Adobe XD.
- Iterative UX design, eye tracking, analytics & user testing.
- have knowledge of photoshop and illustrator

#### **Front End Development**

• UI Development using HTML5, CSS3, SCSS & Javascript, React-Basic.

#### **Back End Development**

- Backend Development with Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Rails Gems.
- Database with MySQL
- Git, AWS, Docker, Heroku, Shopify.
- Basic-Python, Rspec, WordPress, PHP.
- Database Schema Design using dbdesigner.net/dbdiagram.io.
- Agile Project management, Client Interactions, and Project Delivery & Deployment.

#### **Internet Marketing**

- Planning and execution of SEO, social media, display advertising, and email marketing campaign strategies.
- Creating, building, and maintaining a social media presence.
- Measuring and reporting on performance of all campaigns in relation.
- Identifying trends, industry insights to allocate and optimize funds spent.
- Brainstorm innovative growth strategies by collaborating with marketing, promotions, and sales departments.
- Understand search analytics to advise content creators on various enhancement strategies for performance on Google, Instagram, Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, and company websites.
- Designed promotional items like Banners, Posters, and flyers for Ads Promotion.



Website: https://adarshkl1310.github.io/Adarsh/

## LIFE SKILLS

- Presentation skills with an eye for detail, creativity, and innovation.
- High Emotional Quotient (EQ) and instant rapport-building ability.
- Developing new concept websites.
- Viewing and understanding source codes of other websites.
- Ask questions and Answer questions in Stack Overflow (user- id:8540055).
- Strong business and technical aptitude.
- Core team player and a proactive team builder.
- Good communication skills, trained in native American accent and phonetics.
- Excellent professional networking skills and great oratory skills.
- Exceptional Designer and great at creating amazing work quickly and easily

## EDUCATION

Course	Institution/University	Performance
10 th Grade	Pushpa English medium School	54%
Electronics and Communication Diploma	SM Polytechnic (3Years course)	67%
Instrumentation Technology Engineering	JSS Academy of Technical Education	Dropout in 3rd Year

### GOALS

- Being the best professional to represent the company to all its clients and prospects.
- Being a top performer and accepting Agile project management opportunities in the team.
- Cherishing great pleasure in doing the things that I love the most.